Jhal Hello friends, welcome to laptops.
Friends, in this video we are going to
cover the quarter for research date of some companies. Well, let
me tell you that till now, whichever
company has declared its quarter for results date,
we have
made separate videos on them, that is, I have
made videos on each one separately
on this channel, but still some bits and pieces were
left out, so I thought of gathering them
all in one video and making them, so
friends, let's start this
video. The first name here
is Atul Limited. This company has
declared its quarter-finals date.
You can see here that
its quarter for results is going to come on 26th April
and along with that, the company is also thinking of giving a different offer this time.
Then you
see here, just a few days ago, on 25th March, in the
board meeting of the company, the company has
also announced buyback, so now you can say
that this is a good thing for their shareholders.
Now, look at the second company here,
Naveen Protein, this company has also declared its
quarter-finals date.  The result date of the for has been declared,
you can see here,
its quarter final result is going to come on 7th May
and Naveen Florin is also going to reward its shareholders
with dividend, you
can see it here but you know that first the
difference will be considered in the board meeting, the
vote will be approved and then the dividend will be given,
now see here, the proven
IT giant Wipro has also
declared its quarter final result date,
you can see here,
Wipro's quarter for
result is going to come on 29th April and here you can see one more thing,
a few days ago there was a board
meeting i.e. on 25th March
regarding the difference and perhaps for the first time Wipro has declared such a
big difference i.e. a difference of ₹5
for its shareholders, otherwise it gives a dividend
and a dividend,
but this time it is giving ₹5, so it is a
very good thing for its shareholders, now
see the next company here, ICICI
Prudential, this company has also declared its quarter
for result date  It is given
here, let's take a look here,
see here, ICICI
Prudential's quarter for career is going to come on 16th April,
after that, look here, Procter
& Gamble Healthcare Limited, let's see
when the quarter final result of this company is going to come,
yes, see here, the company has
declared the date, the
quarter final result of this company is going to come on 1st May,
now while you are at it, take a look at this company also,
this is also a stock of Procter & Gamble
group, Procter & Gamble
Hygiene Healthcare Limited is a very expensive
stock, you can see here, let's see
when its quarter for result is going to come,
you see it here, the
quarter for result of this company is going to come on 28th April, so
friends, these were some important companies
which have recently declared their quarter for
result date, if you are
new to this channel, then you must visit our channel, till now
we have made separate videos on all the important and popular companies which have declared their quarter for results date,
if you
want, you can watch all those videos,
Friends, that's all for now, please subscribe to the channel
because on this channel we keep
bringing updates related to the share market,
so we will meet
in the next video, till then goodbye.